Not me, huh?
No, I use common sense
If I were a mafia
When you nigga get caught
Why would I stop you?
No, that's not it, I...
Oh, Heo Yul is a mafia?
- you…
- Ah, now, now, now, now, now
Now, now, now, like this
In this way
Dugu dugu, dugu dugu
Good citizens lose
The mafia has won!
- yes!
- look!
Oh, I said I was a citizen.
I don't trust people's words
you did a damn good job
Heo Yul said he was a mafia.
- Was it you?
- Hey, do it again, do it again
Do it again, do it again
It's so fucking loud
Oh, call, call, call, call
Hey, tell them to shut up.
In the next edition, I
It kills Heo Yul first, really.
- hey!
- Do it quickly, quickly.
Kyungjun is sleeping
It's noisy
Those motherfuckers, mr.
Hey, don't do that.
Hey, are you crazy? A pictorial?
How did it look like this?
Hey, are you saying I’m reaching Junhee?
You took a hidden camera
Will you do it?
Just take this opportunity to seduce me.
I heard you’ve been flirting with me since last year.
When?
- Seduce me now.
- Sooner or later.
Hey Junhee
Don't do it
Hey, look at this.
If you keep looking at me like that
Just sit next to me
I didn't see it
Yes, Mr. Kim.
teacher, teacher
- You arrived now, right? teacher
- Yes? hello?
- Where is this place?
- What?
- Around here...
- hello
- Can't you hear me?
- Yes
I can't hear you clearly, hello?
Shall we go?
yes?
-Only half of us arrived?
- Hey, Hyeonho, help me.
give it
Ah…
Hey
Have you ever been here?
Why do you think I came here?
All training centers are the same, right?
Hey, Lee Yunseo
- Huh?
- I'm going
uh
Yunseo Lee
- Huh?
- What are you doing? let's go
uh
Boy, I'm so annoyed, really
Have you decided on a birthday present yet?
tell me today
I won't buy it after 12 o'clock.
Wow, shamefully written.
But I haven't decided yet
Um… Mystery novel?
Uh, that
Okay
Ah, anyway
My cell phone is now
It doesn't explode
Doesn't it usually explode here?
Hey, maybe
Well, can I make a phone call?
Oh, it's not working now.
What should I do?
Should we go?
to?
Somi, that one
Let’s see how talented you are, eh?
- Hey
- Huh?
Stop looking at me, Tina.
I didn't see it
I don't see it
Oh, shit, really.
To this extent
I will make it in one day too
What?
Didn't you do QR?
It was installed automatically.
Give me the phone, I'll do it for you
Huh? no
I can watch this
Do you want to carry that around for two days?
- Prefect
- Yes
Kids in other classes now
Because I have to pick you up
Don't do anything else, go to your room
Keep an eye on your kids so they don’t get into accidents.
yes, i understand
-You too, vice-captain
- Yes
went and came
I need to take a commemorative photo at night
They told me to keep wearing my school uniform.
- Yes
- I'm going
yes
What is it? Why are you so busy?
There is no wifi here
It's completely rotten
But what kind of commemorative photo should you take at night?
That's right
I can't get any signal at all?
child
Hey, he's filming us again
Anyway, I have eyes to see.
It's not us, it's me
What should I do? It's all my fault
Unlucky, really.
Oh, what!
What, what, what?
Hey, turn on the lights
Why, why, why?
Hey, don't play around.
Hey, hey, that idiot really is
Hey, hey, listen, listen carefully
I heard it here?
Here before
They say there was a high school girl who committed suicide.
So
What you should never do
At twelve o'clock I look in the mirror
don't look back
And if you sleep
No matter who holds my ankle
Don't look
You're not protecting it, are you?
Ghost!
hey!
fuck off, crazy
That idiot
Hey, you crazy.
Hey, you crazy guy.
Jol?
Now let's go to the room
Yeah
Hey there
Well, when can I give you the money?
I have to pay school fees
Joo Won Ah
Why are you like that with your friends?
I even paid interest
I told you I would give it to you, Mr.
Just wait a little longer
Until next week...
Mouth! Fuck, really
Are you in debt?
Oh, what
I came here to hang out and ask for money, fuck
Also, did you play Toto? uh?
Dabeom, did you lend me money too?
uh?
Ah, uh
But I can take it slowly
I'm not in a hurry
How much is it all worth?
I'll give it to you
instead
Should we play a game of basketball?
call?
Special lecture on coding
I need to listen
Why not?
What are you doing?
Hey, to me
He said something about reading a book, Mr.
Hey, someone came on a school trip
Are you studying?
Don't show off that you're number one in the whole school
So what are the kids doing?
They make fun of me and say it’s Mensa
Mensa is the name of the organization.
People are called ‘Mensan’
tell me how many times
What is it?
I don't need this
I didn't do it
What is it?
Are you a citizen?
me too
What is this?
Joo Won Ah
I'll go at once
Just stand, let's go
Hey, stay still.
Mafia?
Hey, what is this?
what? fuck
Is this brother's turn to step forward?
Hi, you idiots
Let's start the game now
Is Baek Eun-ha not a mafia?
This guy is so good, it's killing me
Hey, that won't work.
Let's kill it
Go for a ticket? go?
go!
Okay
Heo Yul is a mafia
Let's kill Heo Yul
Okay
I was voted for by clicking on the name?
okay?
But I didn’t even sign up as a member.
How do you know all our names?
I can't even use the internet.
How's the game going?
what? Are you there yet?
It's been a while since I went to see you.
Something must have happened, right?
What if there was an accident?
Hey, Junhee
You don’t know when the teacher is coming, right?
Uh, I don't know because I couldn't contact you.
Can you guys call me?
Oh no
What about the employees here?
I guess they all went with teacher.
there is no one
What? So what should I do?
How long are you waiting?
There will be a phone in the office
Let's go
yes
It doesn't work
Hey, is your coffee leaking?
Did you really see anyone?
Uh, I didn't see it.
Hello
It's cut off
Then 112 or 119
Well, try it anywhere.
uh
Do you know what's going on?
Oh, that's it
They say it will be played during the event tomorrow
Interview about school trip impressions
I'm taking turns picking
What kind of interview is this situation?
let's go
Joo Won Ah
Where are you going?
Ah
That's it
Let's see the kids so
That…
I'm with Joo Won for a moment
I'll go talk to you
- Let's go
- Ah...
It's okay, let's go
Here we go, shoot
Deep three!
hey!
What are you doing?
Hey, Jindabeom, wake up!
- Huh?
- Wake up.
child, Mr.
Go Gyeongjun
Huh?
You're too playful
A joke?
I'm so fucking serious right now
Dabeom prepares for tomorrow's event
I decided to help
Can I take you with me? 데려간다
나, 나
나 괜, 괜찮은데
괜찮다네
아, 나 이 개새끼 진짜
얼굴 하나 믿고 나대는 거
존나게 재수 없네?
Who the fuck are you!
Our Seungbin
Has it gotten a little bigger?
Have you been exercising lately?
child, Mr.
Jang Hyun-ho, this bastard
Why is everyone flocking here?
Are you fucking people?
Do some exercise
Why not?
국대도 떨어진
떨거지 새끼들
어휴, 씨발
그래, 존나 열심히 해 봐
- 가자
- 저 씨발 새끼들
아
저 씹새끼들이 진짜, 씨
야, 하지 마
하지 마, 하지 마
하지 마
괜찮아?
hide, hide
Are you here? Go in
Ah, Yunseo, you go in first.
uh
From the time Yoon-seo came out
Because they were taking pictures
Let's go in a little later.
Take a rough picture
Oh, what a surprise!
surprise
♪ Happy birthday
Happy birthday ♪
♪ My beloved Yoon Seo’s
Think of it as a candle and blow it quickly
Why don't you do something
Are you doing it?
Originally, without even talking to me
child
Hey, thank you
Thank you
We should celebrate with friends
I also have a gift
Let's make birthday bread!
- hey!
- Throw it? What should I do?
Throw it? Throw it or roll it?
- Throw, throw?
- don't do it!
Throw it or roll it? oh my god?
Put it down, put it down
I'm going to cry
Did we go too far?
happy birthday
Are you crazy? What if I push it!
Yoonseo, are you okay?
It's okay
- quickly, quickly
- You go in.
- How do I get in?
- Get in quickly.
Yunseo Lee
Lee Yunseo! child, Mr.
Do something!
child, Mr.
Hey, come quickly and help me, help me out
Come quickly
Yoonseo, are you okay?
Lee Yunseo!
- are you okay?
- Hey, help me quickly.
Ah
I think we were a little harsh
Yoon-seo, are you okay?
Yoonseo, are you okay?
Is there any pain?
Yeah, it's okay
uh
Why are you doing this?
At least change my clothes
I waited to see what happened
Hey, I
Do you know how worried I was?
I thought I was going to die
Hey, what the hell happened?
I don't know
You…
Ah
Are you okay now?
uh?
You can't go into the water
You quit swimming.
Let go! Let go!
ah! Seungyeon!
Ah, ah, that
It's okay, I'm fine
Yeah?
Oh, I gathered the kids together.
I need to talk to you, uh.
I'm taking a break
Yeah
Quickly apologize to your Yoonseo.
Birthday bread?
Hey
You're too playful
sorry
We really just
I just wanted to wish you a happy birthday.
Oh, it's okay, don't cry.
Really?
Are you forgiving me?
Yeah
I'm sorry, Yoon Seo.
It's really okay
Huh? The kids are here
Class president, what should I do?
I can't even contact the teacher anymore.
My phone doesn't work either.
So, what should we do?
Let's sleep in each room first.
I'll be there early tomorrow morning
I'll go out and see.
yes
Guys! Just go in and sleep
Don't gather together for no reason
Okay, sleep first.
tomorrow morning
I'll go out with Junhee and I.
Get in quick, get in
Okay, let's go in!
Kim So-mi, that one
I was just acting with tears in my eyes.
Hey, it's okay, I'm sorry.
Because you keep accepting it
It's not like that.
Well, what should I do, then?
Ah, I don't like it anyway
Oh, you decided to hang out all night long.
Hey, the atmosphere is like this too.
Do you want to play? just sleep
Voting closes
1 minute ago
What is it?
Oh, even broadcasting?
It's refreshing, admit it?
Uh, admit it
But you made this
no
- Did you see it?
Isn’t this a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of
- Hey, hey.
- Oh, it's not me.
Did you do it?
- Uh
-Who did you pick?
Heo Yul?
voting
It has ended
I guess everyone would have flocked to him at first glance?
You did it anyway
what do i do
Oh, and
Why are you picking me, really?
Do you want to play a fun game?
no way!
Most voted, 24 votes
Heo Yul is executed
bye
Ah, tsk tsk
That addiction is starting again, that's it
Stop it
Are you acting again? It's not fun, stop it
- Hey, hey.
- What's wrong, what's wrong?
Hey
What's wrong?
Hey, Gwae, are you okay?
It's okay, right?
Yul, are you telling me to stop?
child, Mr.
What is it? Why is it like that?
Hey, man! hey!
- Hey, Heo Yul!
-Why is he doing that?
Someone please stop him!
Yulia
Hey!
Heo Yul’s occupation is
I am a citizen
Hey, what is this?